这两个窗格已经显示在平板上了
Once the two panes
are showing up on the tablet,
我们来改变处理点击事件的代码
let's modify our code to
handle the list item click.
在手机上，如果forecastFragment里的列表项被点击了
On the phone, if an item is
clicked in the forecast fragment,
然后我们就要载入detail_activity
then we must launch the detail activity.
在平板用户界面上，一旦列表项被点击了
On the tablet UI, once an item in
the forecast fragment is clicked,
我们要通知main_activity替换detail_fragment
we notify the main activity which goes
and replaces the detail fragment.
之所以这两个fragment互相没有关联的原因是
The reason the two fragments
don't talk to each other
我们希望保持彼此抽象
is because we want to maintain
abstraction from each other.
如果forecast list fragment开始假设 detailed fragment
If the forecast list fragment started
assuming that the detailed fragment was
总是在它的右边，那么假设将会被打破
always right next to it, then the
assumption would break, for example on
比如在手机上，data fragment并不是在main activity里
the phone, where the data fragment
is not inside the main activity.
因此，fragment必须通过它的activity
Therefore, a fragment must
go through it's activity.
一个activity必须知道如何把事件分发到其它的fragment里
An activity must know how to dispatch
the event to the other fragments.
记住，一个fragment不必总是
Keep in mind that a fragment
doesn't always has to be
用在同一个activity里
used in the same activity.
为了让forecast fragment与main activity建立联系
In order for the forecast fragment
to talk to the main activity,
我们应该创建一个回调接口
we should create a callback interface.
这样就更好的判断fragment一直在
It's a better assumption to say that
the fragment will always be within
实现了这个回调的activity中
an activity that
implements this callback;
然后就可以确定forecast fragment一直在main_activity里
then to say that the forecast fragment
will always be inside the main activity.
一个fragment怎么可以被用于两个不同的activity里，
The detail fragment is a good
example of how a fragment can
detail_fragment就是一个很好的例子
be used in two different activates, the
main activity and the detail activity.
所以不要依赖getActivity函数来返回一个特定activity类
So don't rely on get activity
returning a specific activity class.
使用我们提供的依据--这个回调类来通知activity
Using the gist that we provided, use
a callback class to notify the activity
列表项被点击了
that a list item has been selected.
看看item click list listener下面的提示
See the hint below on
the item click list listener.
然后，这个activity既可以加载detail activity
Then, the activity can either
launch the detail activity or
也可以替换detail_fragment,这要看是手机还是平板设备
replace a detail fragment based on
whether it is a phone or tablet.
当你做这个任务的时候，你会陷入一个问题中
When you work on this task you'll
run into an issue of how to pass
就是怎么传递选中项到detail fragment中
the selected items you arrive to the
detail fragment, now your instinct might
现在你的直觉可能是创建一个自定义构造器来传递数据
say to create a custom constructor
where you can pass in the date,
然而，我们一般不会创建自定义的fragment构造函数
however, we don't normally create
custom fragment constructors.
比如，如果你旋转设备，系统不能以正确的参数调用
If you ever rotate the device, for
example, the system can't call
你自定义的构造器
your custom fragment constructor
with the right parameters.
但是，可以使用空的fragment构造器
However, it can use the empty
fragment constructor and
用之前使用的同一个bundle初始化它
initialize it with the same
bundle of arguments used earlier.
为了传递信息到初始化的fragment里，
So to pass information to initialize
a fragment, create a bundle of
创建一个bundle的键值对，然后再给fragment设置属性
key value pairs and then set that
as the arguments on the fragment.
不要把arguments bundle和savedInstanceState bundle弄混了
Don't confuse this arguments bundle
with the savedInstanceState bundle.
一旦fragment被初始化
Once a fragment has been initialized,
你不可以改变其属性，就像这里看到的一样，你只能读取它们
you can't change the arguments, you
can only read from them, as seen here.
另一方面，save state bundle是为了
On the other hand the save
state bundle is for
简化信息，一旦fragment运行起来
storing information once
a fragment has been running, and
你可以将它植入onSaveInstantState函数
you can populate it in the on
save instant state method.
bundle可以在横屏与竖屏间保持状态，
The bundle can preserve state
across orientation changes or
否则fragment或者activity会被系统杀掉
if the fragment or
activity gets killed by the system,
这就是为什么我们要在onCreate或者onCreateView里重新接收它的原因
that's why you receive it back again in
the onCreate or onCreateView methods.
一旦fragment显示在平板上
Once the detail fragment starts
being displayed on the tablet,
我们需要确保位置变化时不能丢失数据
we need to make sure that doesn't get
out of date if the location changes.
如果用户设置了一个新的位置
If the user went to Settings and
当他们回到main_activity里
entered in a new location, when they
come back to the main activity,
在onResume函数里，我们应该发觉位置已经变化了
in the onResume method, we should
detect that the location has changed.
我们是依靠比对nLocation和存储在 shared preferences的
We do this by comparing
the nLocation string
字符串来做到这个的
with the location that's
stored in shared preferences.
如果不一样，那我们找到ForecastFragment
If there's a difference,
then we find the ForecastFragment and
通知位置已经变化了
notify that the location has changed.
同样的，找到DetailFragment，通知位置
Similarly, we find
the DetailFragment and
已经变化了
notify that the location has changed.
因为DetailFragment是动态添加的
Since the DetailFragment is
a dynamically added fragment,
我们应该保证找到正确的FragmentManager的实例
we need to make sure we find the right
instance in the FragmentManager.
通过调用findFragmentByTag，传入tag参数
We do this by calling findFragmentByTag
and passing in this tag.
我们结合这个fragment里的tag
We associated this tag
with this fragment
在我们第一次处理这个fragment，把它添加到屏幕上的时候
when we first did the fragment
transaction to add it to the screen.
如果你还没有创建一个tag,
If you didn't already create a tag and
并将它与detail_fragment联系起来
associate it with the detail fragment
in the fragment transaction,
那么现在就做好它，在main activity里的onCreate函数里
then go ahead and do it now in the
onCreate method of the main activity.
你会注意到detail_fragment的tag只是一个字符串
And you'll notice that the detail
fragment tag is just declared as
它声明在类文件的最上面
a string at the top of the file.
在改好main_activity后
After we make the changes
to the main activity
再去改detail_fragment
we go over to the detail fragment,
我们添加了一个新的方法，叫做onLocationChanged，接收一个位置字符串参数
we add a new method onLocationChanged
that takes in a new location string.
首先，我们尝试指出
First, we try to figure
out what is the date for
当前显示的数据是什么
the data that we're currently showing.
然后使用新的位置创建一个新的URI
Then we create a new Uri
with the new location,
就像我们已经显示出的数据一样
as well as the date we're
already displaying.
更新这个URI，重新载入
We update the nUri and
then we restart the loader.
看看板书上涉及处理位置改变的代码
See the instructor notes for the code
related to handling the location change.
这才是这个app完成时该有的样子
This is what the app should
look like when you're done.
当你点击不同的数据，它自动更新窗格
When you tap on a different date,
it updates the detail pane.
你可以移除所有辛苦创建的数据，因为布局现在
You can remove any hard coded data
because the layout should be populated
可以动态植入了
dynamically now.